

# **Abiodun Segun**

Frontend Developer

## INFO

### **Address**

Anipole Street Soluyi Gbagada, Lagos

#### **Phone**

+234-7061541186

#### **Email**

abiodun\_segun10@yahoo.com

#### **LANGUAGES**

English & Yoruba

### **SKILLS**

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Trello, React, Chakra UI, Git, GitHub Good communication skill, Solution oriented. Teamwork and collaboration. **Technical Report Writing** 

## **PROFILE**

Innovative Front End Developer with 2 years experience building and maintaining websites and web applications using web technologies such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript plus modern libraries and frameworks. I have good interpersonal skills, am an excellent team worker and am keen and very willing to learn and develop new skills.

## **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

## Front End Developer, Phasecurve Technology

June 2022 - present

Phasecurve Technology is a Nigerian company focused on developing software to solve real business problems

## Responsibilities:

- Developing and redesigning web pages of the company's websites
- Creating new functionality and features on project using react.js and json-server
- · Performing bug fixes and code reviews
- · Collaborating with designers to ensure design was efficient and technically sound
- · Working with client to develop technical solutions for business cases
- · Agile/Scrum Methodology

## Front End Developer (Intern), identity Pass



March 2022 - May 2022

Identity Pass is an IT service for compliance and security infrastructure for Africa Responsibilities:

- Learning and working with new development tool (GraphOI)
- Frequent design meetings and collaborating on projects.
- · Fixing code issues or bugs that arise
- Agile/SCRUM Methodology.

## Software Developer fellow, The Bulb Africa

May 2021 - December 2021

The Bulb is a tech talent incubator and a platform that addresses the shortage of African tech talents.

### Responsibilities:

- Writing and maintaining code, learning codebase and improving my coding skills.
- Frequent design meetings and collaborating on projects.
- · Analyze the structure and design of web pages.
- · Assembled web pages with basic components using react.
- Track project using GitHub

## **EDUCATION**

National Open University of Nigeria, Victoria Island, Lagos

2020

Degree: B.sc Entrepreneurship and Business Management

Igbobi College Yaba, Lagos

2012

Certificate: WASSCE

Linsy Nursery & primary School, Igbo Efon Lekki, Lagos

2005

Certificate: First School Leaving Certificate

## **REFERENCES**

- Engr Abiodun Olufemi Director of Bogus Worldlink Ventures 08053563731
- Mr Ayobami Joseph Director of Bamyx Technology 08165983685